<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Sirius</title>
  <icon>https://siriusq.top/en/icon.png</icon>
  <subtitle>May the Force be with you</subtitle>
  <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/"/>
  <updated>2025-01-18T13:23:41.831Z</updated>
  <id>https://siriusq.top/en/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Sirius</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Solution to the Prevent Shutdown Issue Caused by Traffic Monitor</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/traffic-monitor-prevent-shutdown.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/traffic-monitor-prevent-shutdown.html</id>
    <published>2025-01-14T13:28:12.000Z</published>
    <updated>2025-01-18T13:23:41.831Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-center&quot;&gt; Use task scheduler to force terminate TrafficMonitor.exe during shutdown to solve the issue in Windows 11 &lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Windows" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/Windows/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Win11" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Win11/"/>
    
    <category term="Traffic Monitor" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Traffic-Monitor/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Enable HEIC Image Preview in Windows</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/windows-heic.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/windows-heic.html</id>
    <published>2024-11-19T12:43:51.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-11-19T15:05:14.000Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-center&quot;&gt; After reinstalling my system, I found that HEIC images captured by my iPhone could no longer be previewed in Windows File Explorer. Naturally, I searched the Microsoft Store for the necessary extension, only to find that the available option required payment. This puzzled me because I had never purchased such an extension before, yet my previous system handled HEIC previews perfectly fine. &lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Windows" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/Windows/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Win11" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Win11/"/>
    
    <category term="HEIC" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/HEIC/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Use Windows Wireless Display to Turn an Old Device into a Secondary Screen</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/windows-wireless-display.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/windows-wireless-display.html</id>
    <published>2024-11-12T12:54:10.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-11-13T10:00:04.000Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-center&quot;&gt; It always feels like there aren&#39;t enough monitors for my PC. However, purchasing a new display can be a considerable expense. I have an old Surface 3 sitting around that I rarely use, so why not repurpose it as a secondary screen? But there&#39;s a catch: older devices like this Surface 3 only support video output, not input, so I can&#39;t connect it directly via a video cable. My next thought was to use a video capture card, which could transfer the PC&#39;s screen to the Surface 3 via a USB connection. However, after some research, I found that inexpensive capture cards come with significant lag, while high-quality ones are nearly as costly as a new monitor—hardly worth it. In the end, I opted for the simplest, most affordable solution: using Windows&#39; built-in wireless display feature to transform this old Surface 3 into a secondary screen. &lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Windows" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/Windows/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Win11" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Win11/"/>
    
    <category term="Wireless Display" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Wireless-Display/"/>
    
    <category term="Surface" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Surface/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Setting Delayed Startup for OneDrive on Windows</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/onedrive-delay-startup.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/onedrive-delay-startup.html</id>
    <published>2024-11-05T09:24:14.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-11-10T09:48:18.000Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-center&quot;&gt; On Windows, both OneDrive and Clash have nearly the same startup time, causing OneDrive to get interrupted by Clash when it tries to log in automatically. This results in OneDrive getting stuck during the login process. At this point, I have to quit and restart OneDrive for it to log in properly, which is quite annoying. To solve this, I decided to set a 1-minute delay for OneDrive&#39;s startup after booting up using the Task Scheduler. Below is the process I followed to set it up. &lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Windows" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/Windows/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Windows" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Windows/"/>
    
    <category term="OneDrive" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/OneDrive/"/>
    
    <category term="Task Scheduler" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Task-Scheduler/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>GitHub SSH Remote Connection Configuration and GPG Commit Signature Verification</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/git-ssh-config.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/git-ssh-config.html</id>
    <published>2024-11-01T13:43:24.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-11-11T13:46:56.000Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-center&quot;&gt; I just reinstalled the operating system and need to configure GitHub&#39;s SSH keys from scratch. Having to search for commands each time is quite tedious, so I decided to record the process for future reference. &lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Coding" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/Coding/"/>
    
    
    <category term="GitHub" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/GitHub/"/>
    
    <category term="SSH" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/SSH/"/>
    
    <category term="GPG" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/GPG/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Windows 11 IoT LTSC Reinstallation Guide</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/win-11-iot-ltsc-installation.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/win-11-iot-ltsc-installation.html</id>
    <published>2024-10-25T11:57:15.000Z</published>
    <updated>2025-01-14T15:33:14.728Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-center&quot;&gt; I heard that Microsoft released the public version of Windows 11 LTSC earlier this month, and I was so done with Microsoft stuffing the system with AI clutter every other day! Without hesitation, I immediately installed the new system on all three of my computers. My last Windows reinstallation guide was written four years ago, and many contents are now outdated. So, I decided to take this opportunity to write a new guide focused specifically on reinstalling Windows 11 IoT LTSC. &lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Windows" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/Windows/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Win11" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Win11/"/>
    
    <category term="Reinstallation" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Reinstallation/"/>
    
    <category term="Office" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Office/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Fix the OneDrive Icon Issue in the Windows LTSC File Explorer Sidebar</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/onedrive-explorer-icon-bug-fix.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/onedrive-explorer-icon-bug-fix.html</id>
    <published>2024-10-24T07:41:25.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-11-07T14:35:29.000Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-center&quot;&gt; After installing Windows 11 LTSC, I noticed that the OneDrive icon in the File Explorer sidebar wasn’t working properly. Clicking on it did nothing, and the properties page was completely blank. A quick search revealed that this is an old Microsoft bug. When you install the personal version of OneDrive on the LTSC version of Windows, the installer fails to register the path value pointing to the OneDrive folder for the sidebar icon, resulting in it pointing to a null value. I guess it’s just classic Microsoft—years later, and this bug is still around. &lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Windows" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/Windows/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Windows" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Windows/"/>
    
    <category term="OneDrive" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/OneDrive/"/>
    
    <category term="LTSC" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/LTSC/"/>
    
    <category term="Bug" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Bug/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>NexT 8.20 Update Log</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/next-8-20-update-log.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/next-8-20-update-log.html</id>
    <published>2024-09-16T04:01:26.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-11-08T15:53:38.000Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-center&quot;&gt; Update Log of my blog. This time, there weren&#39;t many adjustments — just a simple refresh of the version number and a slight enhancement of the reading experience. &lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Website Configuration" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/Website-Configuration/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Hexo" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Hexo/"/>
    
    <category term="Next" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Next/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Hexo Plugin Development</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/hexo-plugin-development.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/hexo-plugin-development.html</id>
    <published>2024-09-12T04:00:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-09-19T15:31:37.000Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-center&quot;&gt; Lately, I’ve found myself a little envious of The Verge’s slick image carousel feature. Let’s be real—when you’ve got an organized set of images, a carousel beats a static picture group any day. Unfortunately, Hexo doesn’t have a built-in plugin for that. So, naturally, I took matters into my own hands and whipped up a carousel plugin based on Splide, designed specifically for the NexT theme. Here’s a rundown of the journey from development to release—because why not document the process while you&#39;re at it? &lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Coding" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/Coding/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Hexo" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Hexo/"/>
    
    <category term="Plugin" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Plugin/"/>
    
    <category term="npm" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/npm/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Silently Launch Steam on System Startup</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/steam-silent-startup.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/steam-silent-startup.html</id>
    <published>2024-08-13T10:06:11.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-13T14:48:34.000Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-center&quot;&gt; Lately, I&#39;ve been obsessed with switching up wallpapers using Wallpaper Engine. However, every time I want to change a wallpaper, I need to fire up Steam to connect to the Workshop. To make things easier, I decided to set Steam to launch at startup. But there was one annoying issue: Steam would always open up to the store page on launch, and there’s no option in the settings to disable it. After a quick Google search, I discovered that the startup behavior is a bit of a mystery—some people don&#39;t see the store page at all, without changing any settings. It’s quite baffling. The solution, however, is straightforward: just add a startup parameter to Steam&#39;s start menu shortcut. &lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Windows" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/Windows/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Software" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Software/"/>
    
    <category term="Win11" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Win11/"/>
    
    <category term="Steam" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Steam/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Block Windows from Automatically Updating AMD GPU Drivers</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/amd-gpu-driver-auto-update-banned.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/amd-gpu-driver-auto-update-banned.html</id>
    <published>2024-08-05T08:06:08.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-09-21T15:29:24.000Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-center&quot;&gt; In a moment of impulse, I updated my AMD graphics driver, only to find that with the new 24.7.1 driver, my GPU started making a horrible whining noise. My case is right next to me, so the sound was like someone sawing through a table leg. I immediately uninstalled the new driver and rolled back to the old, stable 22.5.1 driver, thinking that would be the end of it. But no! Windows Auto Update, in its infinite wisdom, stabbed me in the back while I was grabbing a bite to eat and updated the driver again. After trying multiple methods, I finally got Auto Update to leave my driver alone. Below is the tale of my battle with Windows Auto Update. &lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Windows" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/Windows/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Windows" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Windows/"/>
    
    <category term="GPU" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/GPU/"/>
    
    <category term="Driver" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Driver/"/>
    
    <category term="AMD" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/AMD/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Fix USB Device Detection Issue in VMware Fusion</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/vmware-fusion-usb-fix.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/vmware-fusion-usb-fix.html</id>
    <published>2024-07-08T03:40:37.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-09-13T15:57:48.000Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-center&quot;&gt; Virtual machine installed, 3D acceleration enabled, and XCode all set up — I was ready to dive into some serious iPhone development when suddenly... the virtual machine couldn&#39;t detect my USB devices?! After hours of searching and trial and error, I found the culprit: the vmware-usbarbitrator service. This service is supposed to manage USB device connections to the virtual machine, but for some reason, it wasn&#39;t running when VMware Fusion started. Another quirky bug to tackle! The fix? Setting it to start automatically at system boot.&lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Virtual Machine" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/Virtual-Machine/"/>
    
    
    <category term="VMware" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/VMware/"/>
    
    <category term="MacOS" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/MacOS/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Enable 3D Acceleration for macOS Virtual Machines in VMware Fusion</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/enable-gpu-acceleration-in-macos-vm.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/enable-gpu-acceleration-in-macos-vm.html</id>
    <published>2024-07-07T13:26:19.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-09-13T16:11:14.000Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-center&quot;&gt; In my last blog post, I installed and configured a macOS Sonoma virtual machine, but without 3D acceleration enabled in the settings, it was painfully laggy. Even a simple window resize animation could freeze the VM for 10 seconds — not bearable. After some serious Googling, I stumbled upon a method on the official site to enable 3D acceleration by tweaking the `.vmx` file.&lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Virtual Machine" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/Virtual-Machine/"/>
    
    
    <category term="macOS" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/macOS/"/>
    
    <category term="VMware" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/VMware/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>How to Create a macOS Sonoma Virtual Machine in VMware Fusion</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/vmware-fusion-install-macos-sonoma.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/vmware-fusion-install-macos-sonoma.html</id>
    <published>2024-07-07T02:19:24.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-09-13T15:58:25.000Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-center&quot;&gt; I got backstabbed by Apple! My 2017 MBP can&#39;t upgrade to Sonoma, and since XCode is tied to macOS versions, no system upgrade means no XCode upgrade. The older XCode versions don&#39;t support the latest iOS, so I can&#39;t deploy apps to my iPhone, turning my old Mac into a pretty paperweight. I agonized over installing a Hackintosh, setting up KVM passthrough, or using a virtual machine for ages. In the end, I decided to install the latest XCode on a macOS Sonoma virtual machine. It&#39;s not ideal, but hey, it works!🐶🐶 &lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Virtual Machine" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/Virtual-Machine/"/>
    
    
    <category term="VMware" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/VMware/"/>
    
    <category term="MacOS" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/MacOS/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>How to Download and Create a macOS Sonoma Installation ISO Image</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/create-macos-iso.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/create-macos-iso.html</id>
    <published>2024-07-06T08:56:28.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-09-12T15:13:03.000Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-center&quot;&gt; This blog post documents the process of downloading the macOS Sonoma installation files on a Mac and converting them into an ISO image. Please note that this method is not applicable for Windows operating systems. &lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="macOS &amp; Hackintosh" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/macOS-Hackintosh/"/>
    
    
    <category term="macOS" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/macOS/"/>
    
    <category term="Reinstallation" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Reinstallation/"/>
    
    <category term="Hackintosh" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Hackintosh/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Fix VMware Bridged Network Not Working on Virtual Machine</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/vmware-workstation-net-fix.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/vmware-workstation-net-fix.html</id>
    <published>2024-06-07T14:49:04.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-07-18T08:50:20.000Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;The issue arises because VMware automatically selects a network adapter on the host for bridging. If multiple network adapters exist in your OS, especially virtual adapters created by other software like VirtualBox that are not connected to the real network, VMware might get confused and select one of these virtual adapters for bridging, resulting in no network connection. To solve this problem, you need to manually specify the network adapter to bridge to.&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Virtual Machine" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/Virtual-Machine/"/>
    
    
    <category term="VMware" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/VMware/"/>
    
    <category term="Bridged Network" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Bridged-Network/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Rider R2 5.0 ITX Case Review</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/rider-r2.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/rider-r2.html</id>
    <published>2024-03-23T08:33:10.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-03-25T15:04:47.000Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-center&quot;&gt;After experiencing several fan bearing failures, I developed a psychological aversion to installing FDB fans at the top or bottom of the case. So, whenever I had spare time, I would browse ITX cases on Taobao, intending to switch to a different case. Then, on the second day after Rider R2 5.0 was listed on Taobao, I received a precise recommendation for it. Its power supply placement and other inverted structures were exactly what I had been dreaming of. Without hesitation, I placed an order and replaced my old, stuffy case.&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img data-src=&quot;https://s2.loli.net/2024/03/23/xPpEDrCqBygOb1t.webp&quot; alt=&quot;Cover.webp&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Hardware" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/Hardware/"/>
    
    
    <category term="ITX" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/ITX/"/>
    
    <category term="DIY" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/DIY/"/>
    
    <category term="Rider R2 5.0" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Rider-R2-5-0/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>ITX Installation Experience Summary</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/itx-summary.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/itx-summary.html</id>
    <published>2024-03-16T14:09:03.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-03-25T14:54:58.000Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-center&quot;&gt;I&#39;ve been delving into ITX since the end of 2019, and it&#39;s been over four years now. Throughout this time, I&#39;ve assembled and disassembled rigs, encountering quite a few pitfalls along the way. In this blog post, I&#39;ll summarize the experiences I&#39;ve gained in PC building.&lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Hardware" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/Hardware/"/>
    
    
    <category term="ITX" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/ITX/"/>
    
    <category term="DIY" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/DIY/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Solution to No Bootable Device Issue After Installing Linux on Acer Laptop</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/linux-no-bootable-device.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/linux-no-bootable-device.html</id>
    <published>2023-12-19T10:22:50.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-09-12T15:07:19.000Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img data-src=&quot;https://s2.loli.net/2023/12/24/DWFdJTgk742GY3N.webp&quot; alt=&quot;No_Bootable_Device.webp&quot;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Linux" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/Linux/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Linux" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Linux/"/>
    
    <category term="UEFI" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/UEFI/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>Grasscutter Windows Local Server Configuration Guide</title>
    <link href="https://siriusq.top/en/grasscutter.html"/>
    <id>https://siriusq.top/en/grasscutter.html</id>
    <published>2023-11-07T13:17:07.000Z</published>
    <updated>2024-09-13T16:11:05.000Z</updated>
    
    
    <summary type="html">&lt;blockquote class=&quot;blockquote-center&quot;&gt;Grasscutter is an experimental server written in Java, designed to simulate the server-side of a certain Anime Game. This article documents the process of configuring the server, including the installation of Grasscutter and Cultivation, the usage of relevant commands, methods for utilizing practical plugins and tools, configuration of gacha pools and shops, as well as the replacement of character models.&lt;/blockquote&gt;</summary>
    
    
    
    <category term="Windows" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/categories/Windows/"/>
    
    
    <category term="Grasscutter" scheme="https://siriusq.top/en/tags/Grasscutter/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
